[{"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 1, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 2, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [9], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 3, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [8], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 4, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [7], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 5, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [6], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 6, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [5], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 7, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 8, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 9, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}, {"body": [{"type": "law-fill", "title": "选一选", "stem": "按规律填数", "content": {"num": 10, "img": "fruits/9c51e61782a968ea70809645cb2ba7c3.svg"}, "position": ["右边", "左边"], "num": 10, "unit": "个", "sort": "big", "index": [2, 3, 7]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-07"}]